收到一个求救信号 像是艘小型运输舰
Picked up a Mayday. Looks like a light freighter.
自称是海岩号
Calls itself the Scopuli.
我们有义务探明
We're obligated to check it out.
是海盗诱饵 清除航行日志
It's pirate bait. Purge the logs.
当我们没收到过那个信号
We never received that signal.
我有事要你来做
I have something for you.
一个寻找失踪女儿的案子
Little lost daughter case.
所以我的任务到底是什么
So what's my contract exactly?
如果朱莉·毛还在谷神星 找到她
Find Julie Mao. If she's still here on Ceres,
扣留她 然后送她回家
detain her and ship her home.
绑架的活儿啊 乐意效劳
Kidnap job. My pleasure.
在离太阳这个距离地方长大的人
Anybody grew up this far from the sun
都不会在意你到底是哪个星球的人
won't give a good goddamn what planet you're from.
真实的天空在你头顶
Real sky over your head
真实的重力把你留在地面
and real gravity holding you on the ground,
他们不会信任你的
they don't trust you.
我们本该没收到的那条求救信号
That distress call we never received,
被标记为了高清信号
it was logged with HQ.
霍顿 你指挥这次救援或者说打捞行动
Holden, you'll head up this rescue, or salvage.
组建一支穿梭艇小队
Put a shuttle team together.
事先声明 伙计们
So, just for the record, guys,
我可不想待在这儿
I don't wanna be here right now.
这肯定就是向我们求救的信号源
This must be the beacon that called us.
转接给你坎特伯雷号发来的A1集束通信
Forwarding you an A-1 tight beam from the Canterbury.
鱼雷已发射
Torpedo launch!
坎特伯雷号 该死 是冲着你们去的
Canterbury, burn like hell, you got incoming.
用真的柠檬最好
Real lemon works best,
如果你以前试过的话就知道
if you could ever get your hands on one.
这是配方中的一个重要组成部分
It's a crucial part of the formula.
中和酸性 让味道浓郁
Neutralizes acidity, adds body,
平衡PH值
balances pH.
大概是这意思
Something like that.
尝尝吧
Here.
一杯完美的咖啡
A perfect cup of coffee.
-这是后天培养的品味 -是啊
- It's an acquired taste. - Yeah.
-所以慢慢来吧 -好的
- So, wait and see. - Yeah.
你叫什么名字
Hey, what's your name?
阿迪
Ade.
我是新来的领航员
I'm the new navigator.
吉姆
Jim,
有件事你该知道
there's something you should know.
霍老大
Hoss.
Hoss!
爆炸碎片来了 扣好安全带
Debris field. Buckle up!
我试着避开
I'll try to drive us out of it.
我们会遭受多严重的撞击
How bad are we gonna catch it?
非常严重
Pretty bad.
是的 甜心 你知道我有多爱你
Right, sweetheart. You know how much I love you.
气闸打开了 气压正在流失
Airlock breach! We're losing pressure!
-快去人关上闸门 -我去关
- Somebody close the hatch! - I'm on it!
快关掉那该死的气闸
Somebody shut that damn airlock!
该死的
Son of a bitch.
我们终于出来了
We're through.
还能看舱外的影像吗
Do we still have scopes?
-一清二楚 -不能跟丢那艘飞船
- Damn straight. - Do not lose that ship.
什么
What?
-天呐 你不是 -我们要跟着他们
- Jesus, you're not... - We're going after them.
-老兄 我不认为 -我们要跟丢了
- Buddy, I don't think... - We're losing them!
别这么做 亚历克斯
Don't do it, Alex.
他们刚刚杀死了我们五十名同伴
They just dusted 50 of our friends.
我们不能让他们再把我们五个也干掉
Well, let's not make it 55.
亚历克斯 我让你去追那个飞船
Alex, I'm telling you to go after that ship.
如果他们不喜欢被跟着呢
What if they don't like being followed?
如果他们从屏幕上消失了
They slip off that screen,
我们就永远找不到他们了
they're gone forever.
他们就会从此逃脱了
They'll get away with this.
你们这是怎么了 我已经下了命令
What is wrong with you? I gave an order!
你觉得现在官衔还有用吗
You think rank matters now?
起来 我自己来
Get up, I'll do it myself.
起来
Get up!
我们哪里都不会去
We're not going anywhere.
发动机锁定  所有引擎关闭
大家都冷静一下 所有人
Let's just take a deep breath here, people. All of you.
无垠的太空
第一季 第二集
By aBu 20170428
谷神星_空间站
\h\h联合国保护区 / 位于小行星带
水量配给不足
Water ration exceeded.
他们这是要让我们渴死
They're trying to thirst us out.
-他们是谁 -地球 火星
- Who's that? - Earth, Mars.
水其实已经运到了 伙计
The water shipment's not late, copain.
他们却不给我们
They're holdin' it back.
看来你很确定
You seem pretty sure about that.
水意味着生命
Water means life.
一船货晚了 人们就会抗议
One shipment late, you got protests.
两船货晚了
Two shipments late,
大街上就会死人
you got dead people in the street.
而且只会更糟
And it's gonna get worse.
记住我的话
Mark my words.
恒星螺旋警局  密码破解
天啊
Christ.
爸爸 麻烦 把咖啡洒在了停车场
Father, bother, poured hot coffee in the parking lot.
家 我回家了
Home. I'm home.
显示我的文件
Show me my files.
复制所有文件
Copy all files.
重放最后一条信息
Replay my last messages.
我想把世界上最好的都给你
I tried to give you the best of all worlds,
你却选择像肮脏的女佣一样活着
and you choose to live like some filthy handmaid
和太阳系的乌合之众为伍
among the riff-raff of the Solar System.
鉴于你已经不打算回家了
Since you have no intention of returning home,
我不得不考虑卖掉狭背鲸号
I'm forced to consider selling The Razorback.
你太天真了 甜心
You're naive, sweetheart.
是时候该回家了
It's time to come home.
求你了 我保证一切都会好的
Please. I'll make everything right again.
天呐 饶了我把
Jesus. Spare me.
显示我的回复
Show me my replies.
你太目中无人 居高临下了
You're so blind and so condescending
而且你永远不会改变
and you're never gonna change.
如果你都不能像成年人一样对待自己
If you won't take yourself seriously as an adult,
我为什么还要在乎是不是你的孩子
then why should I care about being your child?
你要卖掉狭背鲸号 卖吧
You want to sell The Razorback? Do it.
你休想再收买或者控制我了
You can't buy me off or control me anymore.
也许你最恨我的的地方就是
Maybe what you hate about me the most
我总是能让你想到自己
is that I remind you of yourself.
水 量
加油 伙计
Keep it up, partner.
你会到的
You'll get there.
联合国大楼
联合国舰队指挥部 / 纽约市
萨达瓦·厄恩怀特
联合国 副秘书长
你真的把一个小行星带人挂了二十小时吗
Is it true that you had a Belter up on hooks for 20 hours?
他是个外行星联盟走私犯 还是个恐怖分子
He's an O.P.A. smuggler and a terrorist.
秘书长
The Secretary-General...
他不愿配合谈话
He didn't want to talk...
秘书长已经公开否认使用重力拷问了
The Secretary-General has publicly disavowed gravity torture.
如果你想跟那个小行星带人聊
If you want to talk to that Belter,
就把他放进水舱里
you put him in the tank.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am?
我听说过你 是的
I've heard of you, yes.
很多有趣的传说
Many interesting tales.
你也算是个能言善道的外行星联盟战士了
You're well-spoken for an O.P.A. soldier.
因为我来自小行星 就是外行星联盟的吗
Because I'm a Belter, I'm naturally O.P.A.?
我只是个小行星上的普通居民
I'm just a citizen of the Belt.
我为了我人民的未来工作
I work for the future of my people
正如你为你的人民一样
as you do for yours.
那为了我们双方人民的未来
Then for the future of both our people,
我要知道你是如何得到
I need to know how you got your hands on
这个足以破坏太阳系平衡的
restricted stealth technology
机密隐形技术的
that could destroy the balance in the system.
你是指地球和火星之间的平衡
You mean the balance between Earth and Mars.
无论怎样 都不会对小行星带人有什么好处
Either way, it's a lousy deal for Belters.
外行星联盟通过暴力来表达诉求
The O.P.A. demands legitimacy through violence.
他们没选择过其他方法
They haven't earned it any other way.
是吗 你现在隔着块玻璃跟我说话
No? You talk to me through a piece of glass,
你看我的身体 已经无法
you see my body which can no longer survive
在这个孕育过我曾祖母的星球上存活
on the very planet that bore my great-grandmother.
地球在太空中造就了一群流亡者
Earth has created a race of exiles out in space,
他们无家可归
who have no homes to return to.
这个问题只能被无视吗
Should this go unanswered?
我并不想让你害怕 夫人
I don't mean to make you afraid, madame.
我让你觉得我害怕了吗
Have I given you the impression that I'm afraid?
那为什么要在我这个小信使身上浪费时间
Then why waste your time on a meaningless courier like myself?
你太谦虚了 孩子
You're too modest, child.
有人委托你运送圣杯的一些碎片
Someone entrusted you to transport pieces of the Holy Grail.
问题是 谁委托的你
The question is, who?
有很多比这里更难过的地方
There are places far worse than this.
我想在某个地方有一位母亲
And I imagine there is a mother somewhere
很想再见到她的儿子
who'll love to see her boy again.
是这样的 夫人
Est cela ?a, madame.
我理解
I understand.
我们都有我们的责任
We all have our duty.
穿梭舰_骑士号
小行星带
我们的无线电坏了 氧气大概还够用四小时
We've got a dead radio and about four hours of oxygen left.
亚历克斯 我们的燃料还有多少
Alex, how much burn do we have?
我大概能开到距离木卫三空间站
I could get us maybe a third of the way
还差三分之二的地方 或许
to Ganymede Station, maybe.
或者直接飞到运输航路边上
Or get us right to the edge of the shipping lanes,
然后就只能祈祷有人能碰到我们了
and then we'd have to pray someone tripped over us.
不可能的
It won't happen.
没有应答机 我们跟太空垃圾没什么区别
With a dead transponder, we're just like space trash.
无线电出什么问题了
What's wrong with the radio?
主板烧了 而且我猜
Board's cooked, and I'm guessing
外面的天线也完了
the antenna array up top has seen better days.
看看能不能做一块板子出来
See if you can improvise another board.
我出去看看到底是怎么样了
I'm gonna go outside and see what's what.
太好了 我们在里面等你
Great. We'll wait here.
我不想总说坏消息 但是
I don't mean to be a bad news bull or anything, but
气闸坏了
the airlock's done.
外面的门也没了
The outer door's gone.
我们得给船体排气
Then we'll have to vent the ship.
你疯了吗
Are you outta your tree?
我们会失去舱内所有的氧气
We'll lose all oxygen in the cabin.
一切希望都在修好无线电上
Everything depends on fixing that radio.
我们在浪费时间
We're wasting time.
又来了 你又在自己做决定
There you go. Calling the shots again.
我要出去 你有意见吗
I'm going outside. You got a problem with that?
艾莫斯 和他一起去
Amos, go with him.
大家先等等
Let's just hold on for one second.
我们没必要去外面
We don't have to go outside.
我们现在很安全
We're safe right now.
把闸门打开 我们就完了
We open those doors, we're done.
船体可能会四分五裂 我告诉你
The ship could crack apart. I'm telling you...
-谢德 -我只是 如果我们打开闸门
- Shed? - I'm just... If we open those doors...
听我说 听我说好吗
Please, just listen to me. Listen to me!
如果我们出去了 我们会死的
If we out there, we're gonna die.
你要休克了 你要休克了
You're in shock. You're in shock.
你知道会有什么症状
You know the symptoms.
你知道会有什么症状的 呼吸 呼吸
You know the symptoms. Just breathe. Breathe.
深呼吸 呼吸 呼吸
Deep... breathe. Breathe, breathe.
好了
All right.
就是这样
There.
就像这样 冷静下来了吗
There. You chilled?
好了
Okay.
现在 我们要出去
Now, we're gonna go outside,
去修好那个天线
and we're gonna fix the antenna,
然后弄出点声音来 我们就能获救了
and we're gonna make some noise and get rescued.
-好的 -好吗
- Okay. - Okay?
好
Yeah.
注意脚下 伙计们 快到了
Watch your step, boys. We're on the way.
外面情况怎么样
How's it looking out there?
不会更糟了
Well, it couldn't been worse.
总是有更坏的可能
It can always be worse.
好吧 确实更糟
Okay. It's worse.
你不在附近队长很生气
Captain was pissed you weren't around.
她要你处理好这事
She wanted this dealt with.
是啊 这周我真是走运
Yeah, it must be my week.
新的地球搭档
New Earth partner.
吸引了所有"烫手"的案子
Drawing all the "Hot" cases...
请大家注意 空气 水和电
Your attention, please. The Air, water and power...
到时间了
Well, it's about time.
一个小时前你就该到了
Expected you an hour ago.
从麦迪纳过来还挺远的 长官
It's a long hoof from the Medina, sir.
一个星期前
A week ago,
开始出现那种枯萎的绿地
those dead patches started appearing.
我的猜测是格雷加斯的人又在偷水了
My guess is, the Greigas are stealing water again.
有些小行星带人显然不尊重
Some Belters clearly don't respect
绿地在空气和水循环中的重要作用
the green space's role in recycling the air and the water.
更别说这种现象会让总督蒙羞了
Not to mention the embarrassment it causes the Governor.
你似乎很确信是小行星带人干的
You seem sure it was Belters.
这的罪犯一般都是他们
The criminals here tend to be.
你是新来的 对吗
You're new here, aren't you?
我们会处理好的 长官
We'll get right on that, sir.
如果谷神星上所有人都能看到这番景致
Maybe if everyone in Ceres had this view,
他们会更尊重你
they'd respect you more.
给你
There.
现在你可以创造自己的风景了
Now, you can make your own view.
该死
Oh, shit!
你是地球人
You're an Earther.
但我都不知道你来自哪里
And I don't even know where you're from.
再过几个小时 我们就成太空垃圾了
We're gonna be space trash in a few hours
你这会才想套近乎吗
and you wanna start a friendship?
你要是觉得我们成不了
If you don't think we're gonna make it,
那你出来干嘛
what are you doing up here?
奈奥米让我出来 我就出来了
Naomi told me to, so I am.
就我看来 她现在是船长
As far as I'm concerned, she's the cap now.
直到弄丢我的小克莱门汀
Till I lost my Clementine
亚历克斯 给E-12送点燃料
Alex, send me some juice to E-12.
-我多想念她 -亚历克斯
- How I missed her... - Alex?
亚历克斯
Alex!
E-12
E-12.
收到
Copy that.
好了 甜心
There you go, sugar.
你没事吧
You doin' okay up there?
我好得就像阳光明媚的
I'm doing as good as dew on
清晨里的一颗露珠
a mornin' full of sunshine.
你和奈奥米是怎么回事
Hey, what's the deal with you and Naomi?
你俩是一对吗
You two an item or something?
一对
An item?
这不关我的事 不过...
Hey, it's none of my business, but...
你一定以为我挺傻的吧
You must think I'm pretty stupid, don't you?
没错
I mean, you're right.
我闭着眼都可以
I can take a core apart
把飞船核心拆散再装回去
and put it back together with my eyes closed.
可要问我应不应该
But ask me whether or not I should
扯下你的头盔 把你踢走
rip your helmet off and kick you off this bucket,
我竟然想不出一个该或是不该的理由
and I couldn't give you a reason why I should or shouldn't.
我只知道奈奥米不会喜欢
Except Naomi wouldn't like it.
可以把钻头给我吗
Could you pass me the drill?
谢谢
Thank you.
我丢了我的小克莱门汀
Then I lost my Clementine
亚历克斯 你在干什么
Alex, what are you doing?
我在带她回家 小圆派
I'm bringin' her home, honey-pie.
一步 两步 我们就能在一起了
One more, two... And we'll be together.
就再去一趟木卫三 亲爱的
Just one trip to Ganymede, sweetheart.
别这样嘛甜心 我在回来了
Oh, don't be like that, sugar, I said I'm comin' home.
-亚历克斯 -谢德 他怎么了
- Alex. - Shed, what's wrong with him?
他缺氧了
He's, uh... He's hypoxic.
该死
Oh, shit!
他的呼吸器不行了
His breather's crapping out!
该死 他还能撑多久
Damn it! How long can he hold on?
该死 他快不行了
Oh, oh, shit. We're losin' him!
我们马上回来
We're coming back in.
不行 我们没有足够氧气再出舱了
Negative. We don't have enough oxygen to vent again.
谢德 照顾好他 做点什么
Shed, take care of him! Do something!
我们在真空中 他穿着宇航服
We're in a vacuum! He's in a suit! I...
你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
没富裕的宇航服
There's no spare!
谢德 你是个医生 像样一点好吗
Shed, you're a medic! Act like one!
挺住 伙计
Hold on, buddy.
听着 我要把咱俩的呼吸器连起来 好吗
Listen, I'm hooking our breathers up, okay?
这样我们就能分享氧气了
So we can share air.
你就可以吸我的氧了
So you can breathe off mine, okay?
谢德 怎么样了
Shed, what's happening?
好了 坚持住 伙计 拜托
Okay. Hold on, buddy. Come on.
坚持住 亚历克斯 拜托
Hold on, Alex! Come on.
好了 呼吸 呼吸 亚历克斯
Yeah, there it is! Breathe! Breathe, Alex!
深呼吸
Breathe it in. Breathe.
继续呼吸 我们真是同呼吸共命运了
Just keep breathing. We're buddy-breathing.
会没事的 没事了
It's all gonna be good. It's all good.
谢德 听着
Shed, you got this?
今天不能再死人了
No one else dies today.
如果不把无线电修好 我们今天都得死
If we don't get that radio back, we all die... today.
好了 亚历克斯 轮到我了
Okay, Alex. My turn, buddy.
我吸几口就够了
I just need a couple of breaths.
这就对了
Ah, that's the stuff.
氧气水平危急
亚历克斯怎么样了
How's Alex doing?
他正坚持着呢
He's hanging in there.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
意思就是他在坚持着呢
Means he's hanging in there!
继续你手头的事 快点
Get on with it. Hurry up.
别看它
Don't look at it.
想点别的事 好吗
Just think about something else, okay?
比如你的孩子 想想你的孩子
Like your kid. Think about your kid.
他们荡着...
Swinging on a...
荡着秋千还是什么的
Swinging on a swing or something.
你是想让我分散注意力
You're trying to distract me.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
我们...我们的氧气要用完了
We're running out of... We're running out of air.
现在呢
Now?
没有信号
No carrier.
该死的
Ah, piece of shit!
连上了
We have connection.
马上回来
Get back in here now!
快
Come on.
-好了 -加压中
- Go! - Pressurizing.
你对我做了什么
What the hell did you do to me?
你救了我的命 兄弟
You saved my hide, partner.
你这个疯子
You crazy son of a bitch.
不客气
Ah, no problem.
我要把他送去月球进一步审讯
I need him sent to Luna for deeper interrogations.
他们预算有限 已经所剩无几了
They have a budget, it's already shot to hell.
我不像你 我得卑躬屈膝地
And unlike you, I have to grovel
实现承诺才能换来连任
and promise and deliver to get reappointed.
这和我有关系吗
This concerns me? How?
你离掌管
You're two heartbeats away
这颗星球的政府只有一步之遥
from running the government on this planet.
但你却不用对何人负有责任 怎么会这样呢
Yet you're accountable to no one. How does that happen?
这孩子不是什么倒霉走私犯
This boy isn't some hapless smuggler.
我认为外行星联盟可能是想获得隐形武器
I believe the O.P.A may be trying to obtain stealth weapons.
不要每件事都当成外行星联盟的阴谋
Everything is not an O.P.A. plot
如果地球都负担不起开发隐形项目
and if Earth can't afford a stealth program,
一帮玩石头的穷鬼怎么负担得起
how can a bunch of rock-tossers?
他们是不行
They can't...
除非找到像火星一样的合作者
Unless they've found a new friend like Mars.
冷战就是不流血的战争
Cold war is a bloodless war.
互不信任 彻底独立
Mutual distrust and complete co-dependence.
没人想改变这些
Nobody wants to change that.
至少火星人是这样
Least of all Mars.
那是另一回事
That's another thing.
我要你仔细监视火星上的所有武器设施
I want every Martian weapons facility under a microscope.
已经如此
They are.
那个小行星带人会喜欢月球的重力的
You know, your Belter will like gravity on Luna better.
那恐怕是他唯一会喜欢的东西了
That's the only thing he'll like.
我担心他
I'm afraid for him.
上帝保佑你的敌人 克里斯金
Heaven help your enemies, Chrisjen.
火星和小行星带
Heaven help us all
要是不分彼此的话 那就是天助你我
if Mars and the Belt decide to share a toothbrush.
我敢说那是大胆之举
Bold move, I'll give him that.
什么
What?
冷战结束了 这是新出现的问题
The cold war is over, this is something new.
天线可以用了 但信号还是很弱
The antenna's working but our signal's still too weak.
发射器没通上电 没用了
The transmitter was severed from the power grid. It's done.
情况真是越来越好了啊
This just keeps getting better and better.
所以我们费了一个小时的空气
So we just blew an hour
就为了修一个根本用不了的无线电
of air for a radio that doesn't even work?
我们不能自己组装一个放大器吗
Can't we rig ourselves an amplifier?
那需要很多电
We're gonna need a shit load of power.
把所有东西拆了
Take everything apart.
动作要快 要小心 船舱已经摇摇欲坠了
Be fast and be careful, we're inside of a limb with a pin here.
把所有有电池 电源组
If it has a battery, a power pack,
以及任何有蓄电功能的东西都拆了
any charge capability, it goes into a part.
怎么了 各位是还得先来个按摩吗
I'm sorry, does anyone need a back rub first?
最后一个
Last one.
就算有人收到了我们的求救信号
Even if someone hears our SOS,
他们也会认为我们是太空海盗
they're gonna think we're pirates.
那么
Well...
我们只有祈祷
We're gonna just have to pray
遇到某个像阿迪一样同情心泛滥的人
there's another caring soul out there like Ade.
阿迪 就是因为她我们才会落到这个地步
Ade? She's why we're in this shit right now.
如果她没标记那该死的求救信号
If she hadn't gone and logged that stupid distress call...
你不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you are talking about.
说话给我注意点
You wanna keep your teeth in your mouth...
这是在浪费空气
We're wasting air.
帮我说句话好吗 伙计
Give me a hand over here, will you, buddy?
你想减轻自己的负罪感
You want to unburden your soul,
麻烦得空了再去
do it on your own time.
我们得救的机会如此渺茫
On the remotest chance we get off this alive.
我们的麻烦已经够多的了
We have enough problems right now.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你知道那家伙的意思是叫你
You know that guy was telling you to go...
自我安慰下的
hump yourself.
天啊 是吗 我都没意识到
Geez... Really? I hadn't realized that.
反正我已经有计划了
I've got plans for it, anyway.
不用问我也知道
Not even gonna ask.
外行星联盟
纹身不错啊
Nice tat.
你老板允许你像这样露出纹身吗
Your boss lets you wear your colors like that, out in the open?
老板也有个差不多的
Boss has one just like it.
这是一条 向花园东南角供水
Here's the one. Feeds the south-east corner of the gardens.
-这个吗 -对
- This guy? - Yeah.
看这个
Look it, here.
传感器盒应该在你们右边
Sensor box should be to your right.
技术一般
Amateurs.
不过敢打公园的主意胆子不小
But you gotta admire their stones for hittin' the park.
这些管子通向哪儿
Where did you say this pipe diverts to?
十二层 冷凝系统 在一个仓库里
Twelfth Level, condenser grid. It's in a warehouse.
如今哪怕是这种水
Even water like this today,
小行星带的承运商也会要
Belter loader gonna want it.
尝尝吗
Sa baka.
味道不错 不错
It's good! Good.
可以拿来卖
We can sell it.
可以赚钱去了
Let's make some money!
恒星螺旋警察 别动
Star Helix, don't move!
放聪明点
Be smart.
来吧 小子
Come on, kid.
你就这点能耐
Is that everything you got?
学着点 警官
Doing my work, cop.
你们这些小混混偷上输水管的水干什么
What are you punks doing stealing up-tunnel water?
免费样品
Free sample.
还挺有精力的嘛
All piss and vinegar.
知道吗 你们很走运
You know, you're lucky
是我们在追捕你们 而不是格雷加斯
it's us chasing you and not the Greigas.
在他们地盘上撒野
They would feed you your fingers,
他们会让你吃不了兜着走的
for playin' in their district.
格雷加斯已经离开了
Greigas gone.
现在是我们的地盘了
This is our turf now.
没人会把他们的地盘丢给一群街头混混
Nobody just abandons their territory to a bunch of street punks.
你知道格雷加斯的人很聪明
You see, the Greigas were smart.
他们吸走一点水 然后卖掉
They'd siphon a little water, and sell it off...
没人会发现
Nobody's the wiser.
但你 你们这群小混混
But you, you gutter punks.
你们惹到大金主了
You screwed the golden goose.
好啊
Okay, man.
教我该怎么混吗 伙计
Schoolin' me on gangsters, que?
没错 人渣学堂开课了
Yeah, dirtbag school's in session.
听好了 带上你想要的东西然后给我滚蛋
Listen... Pick all the pockets you want, roll drunks...
但你要是敢打水的主意
But when you mess with the water,
那你就完蛋了
that's when you're going down.
也许在监狱里蹲上几年他就长记性了
Maybe a couple of years on a prison barge will set him straight.
你想蹲监狱吗
Would you like that?
随你怎么做
Do what you gotta do.
离开这里
Get out of here.
离水远点
Stay away from the aqua.
告诉你的朋友们
Tell all your friends!
我没想到你会来这一出
I did not see that coming.
是吗
Yeah?
那这个呢 你想到了吗
How about this? You see that coming?
有啊
Yeah.
夫人 抱歉这么晚还给您打电话
Madam, I apologize for calling so late.
飞往月球的飞船出了点意外
There's been an incident on the shuttle to Luna.
接着说
Go on.
那个囚犯 哈奇·萨邦
The prisoner, Heikki Sobong took his own life
拒绝高重力注射在躺椅上自杀了
by avoiding the high-gravity injections from his crash couch...
他好像挣脱了束缚
It appears he broke free of his restraints,
当时正值加速的关键阶段
during the critical phase of the ascent,
他知道此时护送人员也得进行注射
when he knew the guards would be receiving their own injections.
夫人 我认为他这是在表明态度
I think, madam, he is making a statement.
但说无妨
Speak frankly, please.
我们曾用地球引力折磨他
Earth's gravity. We used it to hurt him.
他这是在打我们的脸
He threw it back in our face.
想告诉我们发现了什么吗
You want to clue us in?
我们答复的这个信号源不是海盗的玩意儿
This beacon we answered isn't pirate tech...
是顶级军用物品
It's top-grade military stuff.
主板上的序列标记
Serial stamp on the main board.
是火星共和国舰队
Martian Congressional Navy.
那说不通啊
That makes no kind of sense.
这正好说明了一切
It makes all kinds of sense.
袭击坎特号的那艘飞船
That ship that attacked
并没有藏在小行星后面
the Cant wasn't tucked behind an asteroid,
它就在那里
it was hiding in plain sight.
隐形飞船
A stealth ship...
他们为什么不警告就袭击一艘民用飞船
Why would they nuke a civilian ship without warning?
因为他们可以
Because they can.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
我们到底惹上了什么麻烦
What the hell are we tangled up in here?
谁还在乎
Who gives a shit?
我们还是考虑怎么活下去
Let's focus on staying alive.
之后再担心火星问题吧
We'll worry about Mars later.
还可以吗
Good so far?
信号不错
Good signal.
我们还有三小时的燃料
We've got three hours of juice.
好吧
Well...
我们现在能做的
I guess all we gotta do now is
就是开瓶冰啤 等待救援了
pop a cold beer, and wait to be rescued.
没有
Nope.
这些码头没有狭背鲸号的记录
Got no record of a Razorback on these docks.
有没有
Any, um,
有钱人存放自己喜欢的飞行器的特殊机库
special hangar where rich people keep their pleasure-craft?
在谷神星 我没听说过
On Ceres ? Not last I heard.
不过 是有一个我一时半会忘不了的姑娘
Now, there's a girl I'm not gonna forget anytime soon.
为什么
Yeah, why's that?
前一阵
Uh, few rotations back,
她要出行时
some dock-jock was slobbering all over her
有个码头工人对她垂涎三尺
while she was prepping to ship out.
那人一定误以为她的好脾气是好欺负
Eh, guy must've mistaken her good manners for encouragement
就对她动手动脚
and when he laid hands on her,
老天 她直接把他摔倒在地
God damn, she planted him in the deck.
那姑娘有两下子
That girl had skills.
是什么船
What ship was that?
海岩号
Scopuli.
有些破旧
Dumpy old transport.
没有货物 就这年轻姑娘和一些船员
No cargo, just this young lady and a few crew.
海岩号
把船单发给我 好吗
Send me the ship manifest, will you?
还有应答记录之类的
And transponder logs, et cetera?
她惹上了什么麻烦吗
She in some kind of trouble?
没什么她搞不定的
I'm sure it's nothin' she can't handle.
亚历克斯
Alex?
有人听到我们了
Someone heard us.
-有人听到我们了 -没错
- Someone heard us? - Yeah.
在等信息回复
Just waiting for the bounce back.
信息已收取
发送坐标
路径已确认
那是什么
What is that?
船在来的路上了
Ship en route.
有多远
How far?
大概八万公里
It's almost 80,000 clicks.
还真是死里逃生
It's gonna be a hell of a close shave.
我们会挺过去的
We'll make it.
怎么 怎么了
What? What is it?
那艘船 是火星的
The ship. It's Mars.
什么
What?
唐纳吉尔号
The Donnager.
火星舰队的旗舰
The flagship of the Martian Navy.
应答器确认  火星舰队唐纳吉尔号
来完成未完成的事
Coming to finish the job.
我们还把坐标给了他们
And we just told 'em where we were.
其在回应一个遇险信号后失踪
which disappeared while responding to a distress call.
据称坎特伯雷号
The Canterbury was reported
携带有冰块 正开往谷神星空间站
to be carrying ice, bound for Ceres station.
该批货物的损失造成
And the loss of that shipment has prompted
空间站内饮水配给急剧增长
a drastic increase in water rationing station-wide.
一位发言人
A spokesperson...
天啊 毛小姐 你可真会挑人
Good golly, Ms. Mao. You sure can pick 'em.
找到那位失踪的女继承人了
Find your lost heiress yet?
这个
Well...
她不在谷神星
She's not on Ceres.
乘海岩号出行了
Shipped out on the Scopuli.
出发后就失去联系了
It just went dark right after take-off.
不见了
Vanished.
这周失踪的船还真多
The week for vanishing ships.
你觉得像她一样的有钱女孩儿
You'd think a rich girl
不会想把那胎记去掉吗
like her would've had that birthmark fixed.
不好说 如果那是胎记
I don't know. If it was a birthmark,
她父母就会帮她去掉了
her parents would have had it fixed.
那是伤疤
That's a scar.
我觉得她不想把那弄掉
I don't think she wanted it fixed.
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
这是反抗的象征
Oh, it's a badge of defiance.
反抗她本应有的身份
Against everything she's supposed to be.
她跟你说的吗
Wow. She tell you that herself?
没错
Yeah, she did.
听着 只有我们知道坎特号发生了什么
Listen, we're the only ones who know what happened to the Cant.
如果上了那艘船 很可能就出不来了
We get on that ship and chances are we're never comin' out.
除非
Unless...
你要干什么
What are you doing?
给我们个保险
Buying us insurance.
我叫詹姆斯·霍顿
My name is James Holden,
代表坎特伯雷号的五名幸存者
speaking for the five survivors of the Canterbury.
我们的飞船回应了来自海岩号的
Our ship was destroyed answering
假求救信号后被毁
a bogus SOS from a ship called the Scopuli.
我们发现了一个假信号源
We recovered a false beacon
后确定为火星舰队的技术
and identified it as Martian Naval technology.
-那是个陷阱 -你疯了吗
- It was a trap. - Are you insane?
他们会杀了我们的 -我们马上要被带进
They're going to kill us.  - We are about to
火星舰队的唐纳吉尔号
be taken aboard the MCRN Donnager.
亚历克斯 把他关了
Alex, shut him down!
他把我们权限锁了
He's locked us out.
He's locked us out!
你不能替我们说话
You don't speak for us.
我们打算合作 希望这能保证我们的安全
We intend to cooperate and hope this means we won't be harmed.
要我崩了他吗
Should I smoke him?
说吧
Say the word.
不管怎样我们都死定了
We're dead anyway.
任何举动都只能
Any such action will only
证实坎特伯雷号是被火星摧毁
confirm that the Canterbury was destroyed by Mars.
只要这消息能到达一艘船 一个空间站
It just needs to reach one ship, one station.
就能传出去了
Then it'll spread.
别指望了
Don't count on it.
我们处在他们的干扰范围内
Their jammers were in range.
你们现在是火星共和国的囚犯
You are prisoners of the Mars Congressional Republic.
敢动就死定了
Move and you die.